effective project management requires
more than just creating tasks and
assigning them managing boards Finds Its
spot at the Top If you're using fluent
boards you're already ahead as it offers
ample options to manage your project
boards whether you're developing a new
product launching a marketing campaign
or just managing your to-do list you can
make your boards work for you let's see
what fluen boards offers and how you can
manage your project boards better with
it once you're in with fluent boards you
can create a new board straight away if
you are using it for a while you will
find your boards listed you can stay
with the default view and make the
screen full to get a better view find
any board or task easily using the
search option Additionally the
notifications are always ready to tell
you what is going on your project board
when it comes to personalizing your
boards sorting takes the charge arrange
your boards by creation date or title
whether in ascending or descending order
the choice is yours let's get into our
project instantly you will get your task
list with kbon view but you can switch
to the list view for a detailed look the
latest calendar view steps one step
ahead of the game with unique view right
after that comes filter it allows you to
filter tasks by assigning stages due
date priority or embedded labels if you
click on the three dots the board menu
appears you can have a look at the board
details and insights about activity with
ease to personalize a background
effortlessly choose gradients or solid
colors from the library you can even
upload images if you want and board
labels are your secret weapon for
highlighting key tasks that's not all
easily add members or invite anyone from
outside WordPress to collaborate on your
project board then comes the
notification make your mind when you
want to get notified and toggle the
button based on that need to revisit
archived items no
problemo access them with a single click
in case you want to see all Associated
contacts in your tasks access them
effortlessly to manage future projects
efficiently duplicate the board and
reuse it or delete it when the project
is
completed and that was all about
managing your boards in fluent boards
once you're in you will never feel short
of options to make your project
management hurdles into a fun game to
level up your board management grab
fluent boards today and manage your
projects like never before
[Music]